<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>David Crawford's Writings</title>
		<description>Essays on life, business, and technology</description>
		<link>http://localhost:4000</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Reflections on 2022</title>
				<description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;reflections-on-2022&quot;&gt;Reflections on 2022&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I sent this letter to friends around New Years of 22/23.  It’s as comprehensive a summary of my life as I’ve written since I turned 30, so I thought I’d ressurect my blog and put it up here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear friends,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I miss you!  If you’re receiving this, it’s because I’ve been thinking of you, and I want to connect more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2020, I moved to Denver, committed to my relationship with Stephanie and Blaise, and then the three of us locked ourselves in our home and started spraying our groceries with Lysol like the rest of the world.  Since then, I’ve never fully recovered my connections to the many other people I love who live around the country and the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, now that I have a family, I don’t expect things to be quite the same.  But I believe life has room enough for many different relationships.  And the steady acceptance and kindness I’ve felt from all of you makes me believe that we have lots of time together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I want most of all is to continue to share in your successes and your challenges.  To celebrate your successes, make them feel real and important to you, help you see yourself as the heroic protagonist of your own life.  To support you in your challenges, validate their gravity, and give you the energy to face them.  And I hope to be able to share my successes and my challenges with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m writing this letter to tell you about some of the highlights and lowlights of the last year for me.  I hope you’ll have the chance to read it, and I hope I’ll hear back from you.  Please don’t feel obligated to write a ton or respond to everything I’ve said.  Just knowing you’ve received it and it mattered will mean a lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;successes&quot;&gt;Successes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stephanie, Blaise, and I moved into a house together in the Park Hill neighborhood of Denver in the summer of 2021.  Over the past year and a half, we have become a family.  We even added a dog, Scout, at the end of the year.  I received my first Father’s Day card in June.  Making ourselves into a family has taken a lot of work.  A lot of discussion, a lot of vulnerability, a lot of consistently showing up.  And there’s much more in front of us.  But it feels good to have built the relationships we have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stepped foot on African soil for the first time, visiting Morocco in the summer.  We ate homemade couscous with a family living in the Medina (the old city, or the part of Marrakech which lies within the original city walls from around the year 1000).  We saw snake charmers, and spice vendors.  We visited Stephanie’s sister and her family, who speak fluent Arabic and showed us their adopted country.  Blaise’s understanding of the world expanded dramatically, and he got to practice his French.  And all this came after our time in Paris where we visited Stephanie’s “exchange sister”, rode on the Seine, sipped champagne at the top of the Eiffel Tower, and experienced all the other wonderful things that place has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still at Cruise, and just celebrated my fourth anniversary.  In the first half of the year, I was managing three teams and struggling with a lot of people quitting (my bosses, my partners, and my reports).  I spent the first six months hiring in a new set of experienced and motivated engineers to recreate those teams, and finding a new role for myself at the company.  For the last six months, I have been working as a Staff Software Engineer in the Perception group, which is responsible for the software which understands the world around the car as it’s driving, so that we can react to all of the other people on the road.  I am learning a ton and having lots of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from my personal role at Cruise, it’s been fun to watch the company make so much progress this year.  2022 was the year that we made fully driverless rides available to members of the public in San Francisco, and by the end of the year we had over 100 cars on the road, drove 600k miles with no one in the driver seat, had an incredibly high average rating from riders, and launched in two more cities (Phoenix and Austin).  I personally had my first fully driverless ride, and it was exhilarating.  Echoing a statement from our CEO, I think people are going to be surprised at how quickly self-driving cars goes from a rare novelty to a way of life. It’s very exciting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;challenges&quot;&gt;Challenges&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a way, all of the things I listed in “successes” were challenging.  But I think it’s worth naming some of the things that were hardest for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing is to figure out how to fit this all in without having a scarcity mindset. I can often feel like I am operating out of fear, trying to keep all the balls in the air. I worry that I have overcommitted myself and will disappoint people. The line that I tend to use is: we live a full life! It’s my way of trying to switch from scarcity to abundance. But I think the deeper challenge is recognizing my limits and making confident decisions about priorities. If I want to cook on weeknights it should come from a true desire to do it, and a choice to sign off of work, without worrying about disappointing my colleagues or looking like I’m not working hard enough. (I realize this seems like a trivial example, but the fact that it’s an almost daily occurrence is part of how pervasive this conflict is for me.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another challenge is health. I rated my year on several categories and health and fitness were the lowest. I’ve gained about 15 lbs in the last two years, and I’ve lost strength and flexibility. I don’t want to hire a trainer because I don’t feel I’ve earned one, I haven’t made a strong enough commitment to diet and exercise on my own, and I’m paying hundreds of dollars a month to hold myself accountable. I can tell there’s a flaw in this thinking , but I’m not sure which direction.  Regardless, I know that I want to focus on my health and adapt my habits in light of my changing body.  To feel less discomfort and more energy throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;looking-forward&quot;&gt;Looking Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I keep trying to write down what the next year looks like for me, but all I can put down is bland platitudes.  I guess I don’t really know what it will be!  But I’m getting a lot more comfortable with not knowing.  Whatever it is, I hope you’ll all be a part of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll leave you with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YP8KwawXS5k&quot;&gt;this fun video&lt;/a&gt; of Cruiser’s taking their parents on driverless rides, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/stephanieaultpage/posts/pfbid02G8UrJB9UNSqJGChmVBb27BNzEU8iQNsYppyAAQPaGyjZEAG9XdxUrGwvyV6V9A2dl&quot;&gt;this beautiful post&lt;/a&gt; from Stephanie about our summer adventures.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/2023/01/22/reflections-on-2022.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023/01/22/reflections-on-2022.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>When copying business tactics, check the timestamp</title>
				<description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;when-copying-business-tactics-check-the-timestamp&quot;&gt;When copying business tactics, check the timestamp&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who love building products spend a lot of time thinking about what makes their favorite products great.  So it’s very common for startup founders to look at a successful product, comprehend an important principle underlying it’s success, and try to replicate that in their own products.  Great artists steal, after all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this leads to a common mistake—using the tactics of a successful product in the context of a fledgling one.  The greatest features of Facebook, Yelp, and Amazon are &lt;em&gt;capitalizing&lt;/em&gt; on the success they’ve already attained, taking advantage of network effects they built with &lt;em&gt;earlier&lt;/em&gt; growth tactics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your new user-generated review site will not be positioned as “the place to get reviews for X”.  It first needs to be the place to &lt;em&gt;write&lt;/em&gt; reviews for X.  Yelp is about 98% passive readers and 2% prolific reviewers, but at first it had to be 100% reviewers.  What will attract the reviewers, if not readers?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I got to know a guy who is Yelp Elite and has been for years, and I got to meet some of these reviewers.  It turns out one of their favorite features of Yelp is the forums, a feature I had &lt;em&gt;never heard of&lt;/em&gt; until meeting these folks.  Why forums?  Because Yelp has cultivated a unique offline, real-world community of Yelp reviewers in every city, and the forums are how these new friends keep in touch and plan their get togethers.  That’s pretty incredible.  For most people, Yelp tells you what restaurant or bar to try, but for the Elite, Yelp it it’s own community of new friends who share your passion for food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when looking at the most successful companies, we should learn from their history, not their present.  I haven’t found a book on the early days of Yelp (I’d love to hear about one) but you can definitely read about Amazon’s history.  I don’t think they &lt;a href=&quot;http://datacommunitydc.org/blog/2013/05/recommendation-engines-why-you-shouldnt-build-one/&quot; title=&quot;Recommendation engines: why you shouldn&apos;t build one&quot;&gt;started with a recommendation engine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/2013/05/29/check-the-timestamp.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2013/05/29/check-the-timestamp.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Smite the sounding furrows</title>
				<description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;smite-the-sounding-furrows&quot;&gt;Smite the sounding furrows&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Software engineers can do anything we want.  We command a high salary, flexibility at work, can freelance easily, and can start a small business with almost no up front cost.  We’re not alone in this, but we’re on the high end or our ability to choose any detail of our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if we can’t control the way we work, we don’t really have to work that much.  If we haven’t locked ourselves into a mortgage, car payments, or taken on the wonderful but expensive task of raising a child, we can live very comfortably on a fraction of our income.  According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.glassdoor.com/Salaries/san-francisco-software-engineer-salary-SRCH_IL.0,13_IM759_KO14,31.htm&quot;&gt;glassdoor.com&lt;/a&gt;, the average salary for a software engineer in San Francisco is $90k, which we’ll say is $70k post tax.  I’m currently living just outside the city on about $50k per year.  So if you’re just an average software engineer, you can work one year and then take the next &lt;em&gt;four and a half&lt;/em&gt; months off and do whatever you want with your time!  If you take your $20k in savings and fly to Vietnam, you can probably live on it for a &lt;em&gt;year&lt;/em&gt;.  If you’re an above average engineer and make closer to 120-150k, you have even more freedom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to forget this.  I try really hard not to.  With all this freedom, I try to make sure that I make my life an &lt;em&gt;amazing adventure&lt;/em&gt;.  There’s no excuse to be bored or frustrated or trapped at work, at least not for more than a few months.  I’m lucky to have started my career with an amazing job that made me excited to come to work every day.  So I have a very low pain threshold when it comes to career, and I try to keep it that way.  This doesn’t mean I jump from job to job.  It means that if I’m not happy I notice and I act to correct it.  Here’s one measure I use to determine if I’m doing the right kind of job: I see how sincere I can be when I say the phrase “this is my life’s work.”  When I feel that I’m way off, I invoke &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.portablepoetry.com/poems/alfredlord_tennyson/ulysses.html&quot;&gt;“Ulysses”&lt;/a&gt; and move on:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How dull it is to pause, to make an end,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;To rust unburnished, not to shine in use!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;As though to breathe were life.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, discovering the kind of work I want to do has been a long process.  It’s taken me four years and I’m probably about halfway there.  And I think compared to others I’m moving quickly.  Here are some of the things I’ve learned about what makes me happy in my job.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;challenge&quot;&gt;Challenge&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is, I think, one of the easiest things to find in a job.  If you’re trying to do anything well, it will be challenging.  The only way to land in a job that’s not challenging is if the company you work for doesn’t value your department, and therefore won’t put effort into being good at it.  This is why there’s such a substantial difference between working at a tech company and working in the tech department of a non-tech company.  But mostly if you’re a software engineer and your work isn’t challenging, you’re not trying hard enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;people&quot;&gt;People&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working with great people is important, but I’ve learned that it’s not straightforward.  A group of people is not necessarily a team, and if you don’t feel like a team then you’ll only be happy about working with great people during coffee breaks and after-work beers.  Teams have a common purpose.  It’s important for me to be working with smart and energetic people, towards a goal we all believe is important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;customers&quot;&gt;Customers&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My most recent discovery about job satisfaction is how important it is that I love my customers.  The end-goal of any work done in a company is making customers happy so they will pay you money.  This means you’re going to be getting inside the head of your customers, learning how they think, how they work, what are their hopes and dreams.  If you don’t like your customers, you will not like catering to their whims.  Truly loving my customers will mean that I am inspired by the things they do with my products, or the way they react to them.  Personally, this means that I want my products to &lt;em&gt;help people create things&lt;/em&gt;.  This was a big part of why I created &lt;a href=&quot;http://metricadb.com&quot;&gt;Metrica&lt;/a&gt;, and it shapes the product direction substantially.  I am looking for people who are doing cool things, and trying to help them do them better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lean-life&quot;&gt;Lean Life&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Lean Startup&lt;/em&gt; movement is predicated on the fact that a new startup is an exercise in uncertainty.  An individual life is much more complex and much less understood than a startup.  I’ve often found myself paralyzed by options when I realize how open the world is in front of me.  When I feel this way, I start moving in whatever direction seems most promising, and I quickly learn a lot more about my options.  I’ll take the job interview, spend a few weeks in a new city, have a beer with a potential coworker, try starting a new project.  Build, measure, learn.  It applies just as much to discovering a career as to discovering a business model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Come, my friends,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;‘Tis not too late to seek a newer world.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Push off, and sitting well in order smite&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The sounding furrows; for my purpose holds&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;To sail beyond the sunset, and the baths&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Of all the western stars, until I die.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2013 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/2013/05/19/smite-the-sounding-furrows.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2013/05/19/smite-the-sounding-furrows.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>No comments</title>
				<description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;no-comments&quot;&gt;No comments&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not going to enable comments on this site.  I’m not sure if it’s a permanent decision, but I’ll probably stick with it for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a couple of reasons.  First, there are plenty of discussions about content on the web that &lt;em&gt;don’t&lt;/em&gt; occur in the comments, and the quality of those discussions is much higher.  When you discuss an article on Twitter or Facebook, you’re talking to people who know you and your thoughts are much more closely tied to your online identity, so you act more like a civilized person.  And on Twitter, it can still be a public discussion that I can be involved in as the author.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I also think comments are distracting.  I hope to write things here that are worth mulling over, and the first reaction you have should be your own.  If you finish reading an essay of mine and start reading the comments, then you don’t have time to consider what I’ve said before someone else is telling you what to think about it.  It’s much too easy for us to substitute the opinions of others for our own, and removing the comments section is a small stand against that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’ll leave comments off.  But I want to know what you think.  Send me a message at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:david@getmetrica.com&quot;&gt;david@getmetrica.com&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/dacattac&quot;&gt;@dacattac&lt;/a&gt;.  I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2013 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/2013/05/19/no-comments.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2013/05/19/no-comments.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Perfectionism</title>
				<description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;perfectionism&quot;&gt;Perfectionism&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a problem.  I’m a perfectionist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But not the good kind, where you work tirelessly to produce something that’s just right in every way.  No, I work very hard and I try to make things great, but I still make tradeoffs to ship something and get feedback, to release when there’re diminishing returns on continued work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, I have the kind of perfectionism where I make mistakes, and then beat myself up over them afterwards.  I think of all the ways I could have done something better (good) and then tell myself I should have done them that way the first time (bad).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not alone here. I’ve seen this in others—others who are great at their jobs.  The tragedy of this mindset, of holding ourselves to an unattainable standard, is that no matter how hard we work, we never get to enjoy our successes.  We never get a chance to feel proud of what we’ve done, even though it’s quite pride-worthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve thought about this a lot, and have come up with a way to try to mitigate this problem.  I’ve used it with some success, though it’s definitely not a cure-all.  I post it here to get it off my chest and solicit thoughts from others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It consists of being aware of 3 crucial aspects of the work you did:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did you work hard?  Did you focus and put your all into the task, or did you let a lack of motivation allow you to ignore problems you could have solved?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Did you learn from your mistakes?  Do you feel confident that your skills and methods have improved?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Finally, what did you do well?  If you made trade-offs, what was the upside of them?  What did you do to improve the lives of your customers and clients?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think focusing on those aspects allows you to continue to be self-critical, but keep it constructive and still hold yourself to a rational standard of success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw an old blog post on this topic from Andrew Chen, &lt;a href=&quot;http://andrewchen.co/2012/03/02/why-your-product-will-never-seem-like-its-good-enough/&quot;&gt;Why you’ll always think your product is shit&lt;/a&gt;, where he quotes a conversation he had with Matt Silas at Pixar:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt;: “What’s your favorite Pixar movie?”&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Matt&lt;/strong&gt;: *SIGH*&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt;: “Haha! Why the sigh?”&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Matt&lt;/strong&gt;: “This is such a tough question, because they are all good. And yet at the same time, it can be hard to watch one that you’ve worked on, because you spend so many hours on it. You know all the little choices you made, and all the shortcuts that were taken. And you remember the riskier things you could have tried but ended up not, because you couldn’t risk the schedule. And so when you are watching the movie, you can see all the flaws, and it isn’t until you see the faces of your friends and family that you start to forget them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Go read &lt;a href=&quot;http://andrewchen.co/2012/03/02/why-your-product-will-never-seem-like-its-good-enough/&quot;&gt;the rest&lt;/a&gt; and subscribe to his blog.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What got me was that last part: when he watches friends and family watch the movie, he can focus on what he created, rather than what he didn’t. Not only does it allow you to focus on what you did well, but it’s a much better standard for whether what you did is actually good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2012 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/2012/07/14/perfectionism.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2012/07/14/perfectionism.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Post-medium publishing</title>
				<description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;post-medium-publishing&quot;&gt;Post-medium publishing&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I can see the evolution of book publishing in the books on my shelves. Clearly at some point in the 1960s the big publishing houses started to ask: how cheaply can we make books before people refuse to buy them? The answer turned out to be one step short of phonebooks. As long as it isnt floppy, consumers still perceive it as a book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the most amusing paragraph from Paul Graham’s 2009 essay on content vs. medium (which do we really pay for?): &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.paulgraham.com/publishing.html&quot;&gt;Post-Medium Publishing&lt;/a&gt;.  This is a topic most people are still pretty puzzled by, and Graham has some interesting thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He looks at the cost of content over time and concludes that the price has always been determined by the medium.  Unfortunately, he doesn’t include much data here, and I can definitely point to counterexamples.  The best selling movies are more than $20 for a DVD, whereas less popular ones are under ten.  New albums from hot artists are $15 while old jazz albums are seven bucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Publishers also get us to pay more for better content by offering it only in more expensive formats.  Movie distribution is all about moving from theaters to rentals to DVDs over time as demand for the more expensive formats is exhausted.  A lot more people will pay to see a movie in the theater if it’s better.  Bad movies go straight to DVD.  There’s a similar progression for books from hardcover to paperback.  So, yes, we’re paying based on medium, but the available medium is governed by the quality of the content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t really make sense that consumers are all accidentally valuing the paper instead of the words.  It’s definitely true that consumers are not willing to pay for content online, but I don’t think that’s a change in consumer thinking.  Consumers have always been unwilling to pay for something that they can get for free somewhere else.  What’s changed is that there are way more companies willing to offer content for free or almost free than there have ever been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, this is because the cost of distribution is almost free.  The best discussion of this that I’ve seen has come from Clay Shirky.  From &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shirky.com/weblog/2009/03/newspapers-and-thinking-the-unthinkable/&quot;&gt;Newspapers and Thinking the Unthinkable&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you want to know why newspapers are in such trouble, the most salient fact is this: Printing presses are terrifically expensive to set up and to run. This bit of economics, normal since Gutenberg, limits competition while creating positive returns to scale for the press owner, a happy pair of economic effects that feed on each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Shirky points out, during a revolution, everything breaks before new things come to replace them.  And the change in economics means that the value of the publishing market is probably just objectively lower than it used to be… it’s just way easier to do.  The value has moved from publishing to internet infrastructure.  And that industry will be much bigger than publishing, because it generates vastly more wealth for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2011 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/2011/09/11/post_medium-publishing.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2011/09/11/post_medium-publishing.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
